About a year ago, I was in rehab like any normal kid.
One day, one of the guys I was close with decided to go outside and shit in a bowl.
As we gathered around, we witnessed pure and genuine art being created.
The way the shit plastered out and sprayed was just magnificent.
We saw one of the workers, we'll call him Jumbo, coming so we all sped away, the main
culprit grabbing the shit in bow.
We all made our way inside and scattered across the house.
Me and another kid grabbed the stocking and found the shitter.
We handed the stocking over and faster than I could comprehend, the shit was already seeping
to the bottom of the stocking.
A different worker than earlier, who we can call Joe, came over and shrieked at the smell.
So I and the kid I was with grabbed the stocking and hung it up on the coat rack by the front
door.
The worker from the beginning of the story, Jimmy, saw it and was befumbled by the roasted
shit being insulated in its own heat by the stocking.
I de say that was about the only the only thing I remember from that place.
Cheers ex.